[
  {
    "question": "What is Software?",
    "choices": [
      "systems that are marketed and sold to any customer who wishes to buy them.",
      "Software that is commissioned by a specific customer to meet their own needs.",
      "Software that is not commissioned by a specific customer to meet their own needs.",
      "The product that software professionals build and then support over the long term."
    ],
    "answer": "The product that software professionals build and then support over the long term."
  },
  {
    "question": "Characterized by “number crunching “algorithms such as automotive stress analysis, molecular biology, orbital dynamics etc.",
    "choices": [
      "System Software",
      "Engineering / Scientific Software",
      "Mobile Software",
      "Application Software"
    ],
    "answer": "Engineering / Scientific Software"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is AI?",
    "choices": [
      "stand-alone programs for specific needs",
      "focus on a limited marketplace to address mass consumer market.",
      "software uses non-numerical algorithm to solve complex problem."
    ],
    "answer": "software uses non-numerical algorithm to solve complex problem."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is data structures?",
    "choices": [
      "No answer text provided.",
      "enable the programs to adequately store and manipulate information",
      "describes the operation and use of the programs.",
      "executed provide desired features, function, and performance"
    ],
    "answer": "enable the programs to adequately store and manipulate information"
  },
  {
    "question": "Planning: creates a “Sketch” defines the work by describing the tasks, risks and resources, work products and work schedule.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "It concerned with cost-effective software development.",
    "choices": [
      "System Costs",
      "Software System",
      "Software engineering",
      "Software Costs"
    ],
    "answer": "Software engineering"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Concurrent Model?",
    "choices": [
      "Good to develop large-scale system as software evolves as the process progresses and risk should be understood and properly reacted to",
      "applicable to all types of software development and provides an accurate picture of the current state of a project.",
      "controllable as it demands considerable risk assessment expertise"
    ],
    "answer": "applicable to all types of software development and provides an accurate picture of the current state of a project."
  },
  {
    "question": "This activity isolates requirements and develops both size and resource estimates. In addition, a defect estimate (the number of defects projected for the work) is made.",
    "choices": [
      "Development",
      "Low-Level Design",
      "Planning",
      "High-Level Design"
    ],
    "answer": "Planning"
  },
  {
    "question": "Planning this activity carry the requirements and create both size and resource are not estimates. In addition, a defect estimate (the number of defects projected for the work) is made.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "High-level design is an internal requirement specification for each component to be constructed are developed and a component design is not created.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software is embodied knowledge that is initially dispersed, tacit and incomplete.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "A number of software process assessment mechanisms that enable us to determine the maturity of the software process.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Linear process flow executes each of the four activities in sequence",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software project non- tracking and uncontrol: assess progress against the plan and take actions to maintain the schedule.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Risk management: assesses risks that may affect the outcome and quality.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "It provides a diagnostic technique for assessing the relative maturity of a software organization; uses the SEI CMM as the basis for the assessment [Dun01]",
    "choices": [
      "SPICE—The SPICE (ISO/IEC15504)",
      "ISO 9001:2000  for Software",
      "CMM-Based Appraisal for Internal Process Improvement (CBA IPI)"
    ],
    "answer": "CMM-Based Appraisal for Internal Process Improvement (CBA IPI)"
  },
  {
    "question": "The component level design is refined and reviewed. Code is generated, reviewed, compiled, and tested.",
    "choices": [
      "Low-Level Design",
      "Planning",
      "High-Level Design",
      "Development"
    ],
    "answer": "Development"
  },
  {
    "question": "Flow executes each of the five activities in sequence.",
    "choices": [
      "evolutionary process",
      "No answer text provided.",
      "linear process",
      "iterative process"
    ],
    "answer": "linear process"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software is embodied knowledge that is initially disappeared,  tacit and complete.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stage patterns defines a problem associated with a framework activity for the process.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stage patterns defines a problem associated without a framework activity for the process.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Net sourcing?",
    "choices": [
      "pervasive, ubiquitous, distributed computing due to wireless networking. How to allow mobile devices, personal computer, enterprise system to communicate across vast network.",
      ".” free” source code opens to the computing community (a blessing, but also a potential curse!)",
      "No answer text provided.",
      "the Web as a computing engine. How to architect simple and sophisticated applications to target end-users worldwide."
    ],
    "answer": "the Web as a computing engine. How to architect simple and sophisticated applications to target end-users worldwide."
  },
  {
    "question": "Software should not make wasteful use of system resources such as memory and processor cycles.",
    "choices": [
      "Efficiency",
      "Maintainability",
      "Acceptability",
      "No answer text provided."
    ],
    "answer": "Efficiency"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tools provide automated or semi-automated support for the process and methods.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Technical reviews: assesses work products to uncover and remove errors before going to the next activity.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "It such as compilers, editors, file management utilities",
    "choices": [
      "Scientific Software",
      "Application Software",
      "System Software",
      "Engineering Software"
    ],
    "answer": "System Software"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a Definition of Software Process?",
    "choices": [
      "a set of umbrella activities- project tracking and control, risk management, quality assurance, configuration management, technical reviews, and others are applied throughout the process",
      "A framework for the activities, actions, and tasks that are required to build high-quality software.",
      "process framework for software engineering defines five framework activities-communication, planning, modeling, construction, and deployment."
    ],
    "answer": "A framework for the activities, actions, and tasks that are required to build high-quality software."
  },
  {
    "question": "A software prototype that identifies basic requirements. (modes of interaction, computational features, processing functions) is approved by stakeholders.",
    "choices": [
      "Solution Context",
      "Problem Context",
      "Resulting context",
      "Related Patterns"
    ],
    "answer": "Resulting context"
  },
  {
    "question": "A standard defines a set of requirements for software process assessment.",
    "choices": [
      "SPICE—The SPICE (ISO/IEC15504)",
      "CMM-Based Appraisal for Internal Process Improvement (CBA IPI)",
      "ISO 9001:2000  for Software"
    ],
    "answer": "SPICE—The SPICE (ISO/IEC15504)"
  },
  {
    "question": "A road map that helps you create a timely, high-quality results.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Linear process flow executes each of the five activities in sequence.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "It focus on a limited marketplace to address mass consumer market. (word processing, graphics, database management)",
    "choices": [
      "Product-line software",
      "System software",
      "Embedded software",
      "Application software"
    ],
    "answer": "Product-line software"
  },
  {
    "question": "Method cannot provides technical how-to’s for building software.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Modeling: Create a “sketch”, what it looks like architecturally, how the constituent parts fit together and other characteristics.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software quality assurance: cannot define and conduct activities to ensure quality.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software development is essentially an iterative social learning process, and the outcome is “software capital”.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Iterative process flow repeats one or more of the activities before proceeding to the next.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Evolutionary process flow executes the activities in a non-circular manner.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Parallel process flow is not executes one or more activities in parallel without other activities.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "It resides within a product or system. (key pad control of a microwave oven, digital function of dashboard displays in a car)",
    "choices": [
      "Engineering/scientific software",
      "Application Software",
      "System software",
      "Embedded software"
    ],
    "answer": "Embedded software"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is a mode of communication between stakeholders and the software team has been established",
    "choices": [
      "No answer text provided.",
      "Solution",
      "Initial context",
      "problem"
    ],
    "answer": "Initial context"
  },
  {
    "question": "Communication: communicate with customer to understand objectives and gather requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Communication: will not communicate with customer to understand objectives and gather requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software quality assurance: defines and conduct activities to ensure quality.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The costs of software on a PC are often greater than the hardware cost.",
    "choices": [
      "Software engineering",
      "Software costs",
      "No answer text provided.",
      "System costs"
    ],
    "answer": "Software costs"
  },
  {
    "question": "High-level design is an External specification for each component to be constructed are developed and a component design is created.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The establishment and use of sound engineering principles in order to obtain economically software that is reliable and works efficiently on real machines.",
    "choices": [
      "Software Programming",
      "System Programming",
      "Software engineering",
      "System Engineering"
    ],
    "answer": "Software engineering"
  },
  {
    "question": "Defines a problem associated with a software engineering action or work task and relevant to successful software engineering practice",
    "choices": [
      "Stage Patterns",
      "Task patterns",
      "Phase patterns",
      "Process Patterns"
    ],
    "answer": "Task patterns"
  },
  {
    "question": "Define Open source?",
    "choices": [
      "the Web as a computing engine. How to architect simple and sophisticated applications to target end-users worldwide.",
      "pervasive, ubiquitous, distributed computing due to wireless networking. How to allow mobile devices, personal computer, enterprise system to communicate across vast network.",
      ".” free” source code opens to the computing community (a blessing, but also a potential curse!)"
    ],
    "answer": ".” free” source code opens to the computing community (a blessing, but also a potential curse!)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Systems that are marketed and sold to any customer who wishes to buy them.",
    "choices": [
      "Data consolidation",
      "Generic products",
      "Customized products",
      "Data structures"
    ],
    "answer": "Generic products"
  },
  {
    "question": "Deployment: Delivered to the customer who not evaluates the products and will not provide feedback based on the evaluation.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Planning this activity isolates requirements and develops both size and resource estimates. In addition, a defect estimate (the number of defects projected for the work) is made.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Measures and centimeter should not provide guidance for modifying the process to improve its effectiveness.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "A generic standard that applies to any organization that wants to improve the overall quality of the products, systems, or services that it provides.",
    "choices": [
      "SPICE—The SPICE (ISO/IEC15504)",
      "No answer text provided.",
      "CMM-Based Appraisal for Internal Process Improvement (CBA IPI)",
      "ISO 9001:2000  for Software"
    ],
    "answer": "ISO 9001:2000  for Software"
  },
  {
    "question": "Formal user verification methods are applied to cover errors in the design.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software Process  is a collection of the unfamiliar activities, actions and tasks that are not performed when some work product is to be created.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Defines a problem associated with a framework activity for the process. It includes multiple task patterns as well.",
    "choices": [
      "No answer text provided.",
      "Stage Patterns",
      "Phase patterns",
      "Task patterns"
    ],
    "answer": "Stage Patterns"
  },
  {
    "question": "Process layer as the foundation defines a framework with activities for effective delivery of software engineering technology.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "External specifications for each component to be constructed are developed and a component design is created.",
    "choices": [
      "Planning",
      "Low-Level Design",
      "High-Level Design",
      "Development"
    ],
    "answer": "High-Level Design"
  },
  {
    "question": "SP defines the approach that is taken as software is engineered.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Process layer as the foundation defines a framework without activities and not effective delivery of software engineering technology.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tools cannot provide automated or semi-automated not support for the process and methods.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Its characteristics that make it different from other things human being build.",
    "choices": [
      "Featured System",
      "Featured Software",
      "Featured Costs",
      "Featured Hardware"
    ],
    "answer": "Featured Software"
  }
]